Their only way out is the enemy.
In Enemy Hands is a war film directed by Tony Giglio.
At the height of Hitler's infamous U-boat war, the crew of the U.S.S.
Swordfish were heading home after months at sea.
They never made it.
Now prisoners of war aboard U-boat 429, a small group of American survivors will find their loyalties put to the
ultimate test when they're forced to join their German captors to fight for their very lives.
Nathan Travers, played by William H. Macy.
Jonas Herdt, played by Til Schweiger.
Randall Sullivan, played by Scott Caan.
Ludwig Cremer, played by Thomas Kretschmann.
Rachel Travers, played by Lauren Holly.
Admiral Kentz, played by Xander Berkeley.
In Enemy Hands is a 2004 American submarine film directed
by Tony Giglio and starring William H.
Macy, Til Schweiger, Thomas Kretschmann, Scott Caan and Lauren Holly.
The film follows an American submarine crew getting captured by a German
submarine crew and taken prisoner aboard their U-boat.
The film explores themes of mutiny, submarine, world war ii, prisoner of war.